weddingbycolor.com 2016-03-15

# Wedding By Color - Free Wedding Blogs & Brides' Online Community

Your privacy is critically important to us. At Tov Solutions we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don't ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can't stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don't share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don't store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:

Weddingbycolor.com is one of the websites operated by Tov Solutions Inc. ("Tov Solutions"). It is Tov Solutions's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Tov Solutions collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Tov Solutions's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Tov Solutions's visitors use its website. From time to time, Tov Solutions may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Tov Solutions also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Tov Solutions does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Tov Solutions's websites choose to interact with Tov Solutions in ways that require Tov Solutions to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Tov Solutions gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a blog at weddingbycolor.com to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Tov Solutions â€“ by purchasing vendor's listing service, for example â€“ are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Tov Solutions collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Tov Solutions. Tov Solutions does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

## Aggregated Statistics

Tov Solutions may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Tov Solutions may monitor the most popular blogs on the Weddingbycolor.com site. Tov Solutions may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Tov Solutions does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Tov Solutions discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Tov Solutions's behalf or to provide services available at Tov Solutions's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Tov Solutions's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Tov Solutions will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Tov Solutions discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Tov Solutions believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Tov Solutions, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Tov Solutions website and have supplied your email address, Tov Solutions may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Tov Solutions and our partners. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Tov Solutions takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## Third-Party Advertisers

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

Some of the advertisements that appear on weddgingbycolor.com web site(s) are delivered to you by national internet advertising and application company such as Cox Digital Solutions. This company utilizes certain technologies to deliver advertisements and marketing messages and to collect anonymous information about your visit to our site(s), including information about the banner ads they display, and cookie they place on your computer and your IP address. To opt out of information collection by Cox Digital Solutions, or to obtain information about the technologies they use or their own privacy policy, please visit their website at: http://www.coxdigitalsolutions.com/privacy-policy/consumer-opt-out-program http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Tov Solutions uses cookies to help Tov Solutions identify and track visitors, their usage of Tov Solutions website, and their website access preferences. Tov Solutions visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Tov Solutions's websites, with the drawback that certain features of Tov Solutions's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Tov Solutions may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Tov Solutions's sole discretion. Tov Solutions encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
